Guide to the American Wind Symphony Orchestra Records, 1957-2012 AIS.1981.19
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographic Materials, 1954-1981; X.
  - Topical (Photographic Prints), 2.
    - New Orleans, LA, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Nigerian Art Exhibition, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Orchestra on Stage, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Orchestra performing at a football field, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Performances on barge, 1961-1980 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Performances with Fireworks, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Point Counterpoint (Original Barge), c 1960-1970 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Point Counterpoint II (Barge), c 1975-1980 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Point Counterpoint II (Artist Rendering), c 1975 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Proclamation Ceremony, Allegheny County Commissioners, c 1980 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Promotional Images, c 1973 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Publication Images, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Turtle Creek (PA), Cultural Enrichment Program, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - World's Fair, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Other Formats, 3.
    This subseries contains other photographic formats; images are of concerts, performances, the barge, AWSO musicians and other performenrs.
    - Color Transparencies--35mm, c 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Contact Prints, #438, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Contact Prints, #446, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Contact Prints, #7301-7339, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Contact Prints, #7452-7457, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Contact Prints, #7737, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Contact Prints, #8263, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Contact Prints, #10159-10197, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Contact Prints, #10200-10225, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Contact Prints in Color, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Contact Prints, Herb Ferguson (Photographer), undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Contact Prints, Lynn Johnson (Pittsburgh Press Photographer), undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Contact Prints, Karen MacArthur (Photographer), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Contact Prints, Matthews (Photographer), undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Contact Prints, Metzgar (Photographer), undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Contact Prints, Unlabeled, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Contact Prints (Color), Pittsburgh Concert, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Negative, Performance on the Barge, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Negatives (Color), unlabeled, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Printing Plate, Boudreau & Bennett, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Moving Image Material, 1960-1980; XI.
  This series contains moving image material from the American Wind Symphony Orchestra. Some of the film contains footage of the Floating Center for the Arts, the launch of Counterpoint II, and performances of the AWSO. While other film is unlabeled and the contents are unknown, it is likely that the rest of the film contains footage from AWSO tours and performances, or of AWSO special events.
  - American Wind Symphony, revised [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 1)
  - AWS, old [filler?] [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 2)
  - AWS #6 [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 3)
  - AWS E8952, black-and-white reversible print [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 4)
  - Music on the River, R-1 [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 5)
  - AWS #8 [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 6)
  - AWS #10 [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 7)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 8)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 24, Item 9)
  - unknown [16 mm film], 1976 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - unknown [8 mm film] (Box 25, Item 2)
  - unknown [8 mm film] (Box 25, Item 3)
  - unknown [8 mm film] (Box 25, Item 4)
  - unknown [8 mm film] (Box 25, Item 5)
  - Floating Center for the Arts Launched [16 mm film], c.1976 (Box 25, Item 6)
  - Counterpoint II Launch [16 mm film], c.1976 (Box 25, Item 7)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 25, Item 8)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 25, Item 9)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 25, Item 10)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 25, Item 11)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 25, Item 12)
  - unknown [16 mm film], July 27, 1976 (Box 25, Item 13)
  - Music on the River, Edited (Box 26, Item 1)
  - Music on the River (edit), #2 [16 mm film] (Box 26, Item 2)
  - American Wind Symphony Orchestra at Lake Charles, LA. Unedited work print of all sound dailies, undated (Box 26, Item 3)
  - WIIC-TV [16 mm film] (Box 26, Item 4)
  - American Wind Symphony, Point Park College [16 mm film] (Box 26, Item 5)
  - unknown [16 mm film] (Box 26, Item 6)
- Audio Recordings, 1972-1981; XII.
  This series contains audio recordings of the American Wind Symphony Orchestra, including interviews with Robert Boudreau, the conductor of AWSO, as well as audio from AWSO's performance at Lake Charles, Louisiana and audio of the Point Counterpoint II launch.
  - unknown [open audio reel] (Box 27, Item 1)
  - Robert Boudreau w/ Mike Levine 6/6/72 [cassette], 1972 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Steinbach/ Boudreau KDKA 12/14/81 [cassette], 1981 (Box 27, Item 3)
  - Robert Boudreau 2min 31 sec. Hastings, MN visit 6/21/78 [cassette], 1978 (Box 27, Item 4)
  - Point Counterpoint II Launch [open audio reel], c.1976 (Box 27, Item 5)
  - Lake Charles, Louisiana performance, reel 1 [open audio reel] (Box 27, Item 6)
  - Lake Charles, Louisiana performance, reel 2 [open audio reel] (Box 27, Item 7)
- Oversized Materials, 1972-1983; XIII.
  Oversized materials, including posters, awards, and photographs.
  - Award of Appreciation, Buffalo Valley (Pa.) Jaycees, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Orquesta de viento de las Americas pamphlet draft, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Point State Park concert poster, 1986? (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Point Counterpoint photograph, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)